(upbeat music)
If you look at the facts of what the wallet is doing and if they're carrying out features that are broker like then maybe you have to treat them like a broker but if they're not or if they're mitigated through forms of transparency that aren't present with a typical broker regime, then I don't think you then it doesn't make sense to have that model so I think that's another that's a case where there's an incumbent player that is trying to ensure
that there isn't as much disruption because that disruption could affect their operating model and again like Robin hooded like has lived the life cycle of this right like they previously were kind of laughed out of the room of the syphmas of the world and other trade organizations and now they're
large members of that right and so like I think there is a life and I know we have hot takes and cold wallets here so I think at a certain point there's going to be like Citadel is one of the strongest players pushing against tokenization right now because
they had profit handsomely from some of the monopolistic regulatory monopolistic features of a regulation NMS which allows them to print money by having faster technology and they've made significant amounts of money from that.
So I think like they're also probably going to live the life cycle of this where they're going to push against it because it's disruptive because they already have a very profitable business.
And then once it gets fully adopted and integrated, they're going to be the biggest arbitrage between traditional markets and on chain markets.
And one of the biggest market makers within D five protocols, and like that's going to happen. It's like clear that's going to happen. And right now they're they're waving the flag and saying we need to like protect the perfect markets.
But if you actually look at the markets, they're not perfect. There's a significant implicit costs significant rent seeking behavior. And so I think we're going to see that life cycle evolve.
But it is, I think, not perfect, not perfect is the understatement of the show.
I think the key is always to look at statements that are being made by players and you can do this with Superstate as well. Obviously, we have an interest in a more tokenized future because, like, we think that that's better for everyone.
We also have invested economic interest. I think you have to look at, you know, the motivations of each of their entities and their core businesses. I think it's a great point.
And look, we could spend another hour mining Alex's brain, because obviously you and Superstate are really doing some cutting edge stuff at this topic that will continue to dominate the crypto headlines.
This is a section of trad fight crypto is rarely seen as much as we see it in tokenization.
We only have two minutes left. So I want to hijack the very end of our episode with our crypto good news and it's actually perfect because this week you were just mentioning Robinhood.
I love that Robinhood is a little bit aspirational for crypto because I am old enough to remember when Robinhood was still like a little fringe and not really taking that seriously on Wall Street.
Obviously that couldn't be farther from the truth, in large part due to their stock price, good for you Robinhood and brilliant people like Johan and others within Robinhood crypto.
But one of the things that I really appreciate is crypto good news also highlights use cases, not just good news and Robinhood did something cool a little over a year ago where they did an integration with Daffy, which is a fin tech that facilitates charitable giving
them among other things. But what they do is Robinhood customers can actually very easily donate crypto held in their accounts to Daffy through Daffy's donor advice fun structure.
They use the Robinhood connect feature on the Daffy platform. So what this means is it's really easy to click click donate crypto it's liquidated and then the funds can be granted to the millions of charities that exist right now that aren't ready to accept
crypto automatically now a lot of those charities are working on that functionality but some charities you can't just go and give them Bitcoin.
Hey charities will help you with that. I mean come on like lot of lot of crypto a lot of good people in crypto looking to, you know, help others through the donation of their crypto.
But it's awesome that Robinhood do that did this with Daffy and made it easier for their customers to support their communities.
I want to take a moment to say thank you Alex for joining us. This was an awesome episode chock full of some complicated but very important concepts.
So we will see everybody next week.
When the three co hosts are back in force. Thank you for joining us on decks in the city.